https://www.valleyvet.com/si_privacy.html

Your use of the Valley Vet Supply website is governed by our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Please read them carefully before browsing or using the site. If you are using a screen reader and are having problems using this website, please call 800-370-4838 for assistance.
Call 800-419-9524
Price Match
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: January 23, 2020.
Introduction
This privacy policy applies to all website and mobile applications linking to or posting this privacy policy that are operated by Valley Veterinary Clinic, Ltd., d/b/a Valley Vet Supply ("Valley Vet," "us," "we," or "our"), which are collectively referred to in this privacy policy as the Site.
In this privacy policy, we describe Valley Vet's practices for collecting, storing, using, and disclosing the personal and other information that we may obtain about you through the Site, or through your other communications with Valley Vet.
Please note that by using or accessing the Site, or communicating with Valley Vet by telephone, mail, email, or otherwise, you consent to the collection, storage, use, and disclosure practices described in this privacy policy.
For ease of reference, you may click on any of the following links to jump to one of the topics addressed in this privacy policy:
Information We Collect
How We Use Information We Collect
When Information We Collect May Be Disclosed to Third Parties
Security Measures for Information We Collect
How to Correct or Update Information We Have Collected About You
How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals
Transfer of Data from Outside the United States
Children
Privacy Policies of any Linked Website or Other Parties
Personal Information Requests
Personal Information We Have Sold In the Last 12 Months
Personal Information We Have Disclosed For a Business Purpose in the Last 12 Months
Governing Law, Jurisdiction, and Dispute Resolution
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Information We Collect
Purchases and Other Financial Transactions.
When you make a purchase or engage in any other financial transaction, you will be asked to provide information necessary to facilitate the transaction, such as your name, credit card or debit card number, associated security code, telephone number, billing address, email address, and shipping address.
Program Registration.
In connection with your registration or other interaction online with one of our programs, you may be asked to provide certain personal information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, and date of birth or age-as well as information about your pet-and to create a user name and password.
Sign-Up for Emails, Newsletters, or Other Correspondence.
If you sign up on the Site to receive email communications, newsletters, or other correspondence from us, you may be asked to provide us with your name, email address, and mailing address, along with other information related to your subscription or correspondence.
Contests, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions.
We may collect information about you when you participate in a promotion that we sponsor, such as a contest or sweepstakes (which we may sponsor alone, or co-sponsor with one or more third parties).
To participate in one of our promotions, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, mailing address, and other contact information.
For some promotions, we may request other information about you as well.
Your participation will be subject to the official rules of the promotion, as well as this privacy policy, and the privacy policy of any co-sponsor.
Interactive Forums.
You and other users may be allowed to post comments and other content on certain portions of the Site, such as on a discussion board, blog, or other interactive forum.
We may collect any information that you or another user posts about you on the Site-including personal information about you-and it may be available to all users who have access to the Site.
Please keep this in mind when considering what information to post to the Site.
Social Networking Activities.
The Site may include the ability for you and other users to link to one or more social networking platforms (such as Facebook or Twitter).
We may receive information about you when you choose to post or otherwise share information about us on any of these social networking platforms.
Any information that you or others post to a social networking platform will be accessible by any users of the platform, subject to its terms of service and privacy policy.
Social Sign-In.
The Site may incorporate functionality enabling you to sign-on using your login information from a social networking platform, in lieu of creating a new login account specifically for the Site.
If we incorporate such functionality and you use it to sign into the Site, we may collect information about you from the social networking platform, such as your list of friends, "likes," and interests, as well as your contact information.
Usage Data.
When you use or access the Site, we may collect certain usage data generated by your activities on the Site, including your search terms, page views, purchasing history, credit card chargeback data, pages viewed, number of bytes transferred, hyperlinks clicked, and other actions you take on the Site.
The Site may also track the URL that you visit before you come to the Site, the URL that you go to next, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address or mobile device identifier.
Location and Device Data.
We collect information about your location, such as the approximate location of your computer, phone, or other device (geolocation)from which you access the Site, as well as your IP address, and related data.
We may associate information we collect from your different devices, which helps us provide consistent services and experiences across your devices.
Some examples of the device information we collect are attributes such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, battery and signal strength, and device identifiers; device locations, including geographic locations through GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals; and connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number, and IP address.
Online Information-Gathering Tools.
We use cookies, mobile advertising identifiers, web beacons, and other online information-gathering tools in connection with the Site-including Google advertising cookies and identifiers to enable the collection of Google Analytics data for web traffic on the Site.
These tools are intended to make using the Site easier in various ways, such as saving your preferences for you.
We may also use cookies to deliver content tailored to your interests.
If your browser is set to reject cookies, or if your browser notifies you that you are about to receive a cookie and you reject it, then your use of the Site may not be as efficient as if the cookies were enabled.
For example, if you have chosen to enable Google to associate your web and app browsing history with your Google account, and to use information from your Google account to personalize ads, Google will use data from you while signed-in to your Google account (personal information), together with Google Analytics advertising cookies and identifiers to tailor ads to your indicated preferences, across your devices.
We do not share information that personally identifies you (information such as your name or email address that can by itself be used to contact or identify you) with advertising measurement or analytics partners unless you give us permission.
We may provide these partners with information about the reach and effectiveness of their advertising without providing information that personally identifies you, or if we have aggregated the information so that it does not personally identify you.
You may opt-out of Google Analytics by following Google's opt-out instructions.
Third-Party Integrated Services.
We may incorporate third-party ads and other third-party content on the Site, and integrate other third-party offerings into the Site, enabling certain such third parties to collect information about you or your online activities across other websites and, over time, through your use of the Site. For example, Google uses cookies to serve the Google Reviews badge on the Site, and to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Site.
You may opt-out of Google's use of cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Site by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. Except as otherwise described in this privacy policy, any information collected through such integrated technologies is collected directly by these third parties for use by such third parties and other authorized parties, subject to the privacy policies of those other parties.
Online Inquiries and Correspondence.
When you submit an inquiry or otherwise correspond through the Site, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, and other personal information to us.
Voice Recordings.
We collect voice recordings of calls made to the Valley Vet Pharmacy for quality control and regulatory purposes.
Live Chat.
When you communicate with us online through the Live Chat interface, we collect these communications for customer service, processing personal information requests, compliance records, and training purposes.
Valley Vet Supply may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted service providers. These service providers may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that Valley Vet Supply may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail.
We may keep the information we collect about you indefinitely.
How We Use Information We Collect
We may use information we collect about you for a variety of commercial purposes.
For example, we may use such information to:
process payment transactions and provide fraud detection, prevention, and scoring services;
administer and improve the Site and businesses;
promote our products and services to you, as well as the products and services of our affiliates;
promote, and enable the promotion of third-party products and services to you that we think you may find interesting and valuable;
deliver email communications, newsletters, and other correspondence to which you subscribe;
communicate with you about our contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions;
conduct other marketing activities;
communicate with you regarding your membership in one of our programs, and facilitate the functioning of our programs; and
respond to your inquiries and other correspondence, or request that you provide feedback to us.
When Information We Collect May Be Disclosed to Third Parties
We disclose to third parties the personal or other information collected about you either (1) when we have otherwise secured your permission to do so, or (2) in any of the following situations, with your permission based on this disclosure:
We may share your order information with select vendors and manufacturers to assist them in their sales and marketing efforts; to facilitate reporting and information sharing regarding adverse drug events and disease control; and to expedite rebate calculation and payment services. For example, we may share the quantities of products you purchase; your full name; your HIN (Health Industry Number); your bill-to and ship-to addresses; your zip code; the date of sale; the invoice number; and the unit quantity and sales price per product and per order.
We may share the information collected about you within the Valley Vet family of companies-which means we may disclose the information collected about you to our affiliates, subject to the terms of this privacy policy.
We may disclose the information collected about you to our third-party contractors and partners in connection with their performance of services or other activities in support of the Site and our businesses, or their completing or confirming on our behalf a transaction or series of transactions that you conduct with us.
For example, your credit or debit card number and expiration date, name, address, transaction amount, chargeback data, browsing and transaction history, computer location, and IP address and related data may be collected and provided to our merchant payment processor and its vendors, agents, suppliers, and contractors for the purpose of processing payment transactions and providing fraud detection, prevention, and scoring services.
Information about you that is collected by third-party ads, content, or technologies integrated with the Site may be disclosed to such third parties.
We may disclose the results of aggregated data about you and other users of the Site without restriction.
In these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you.
We may disclose to one or more third parties the information collected about you as part of a potential or complete merger, acquisition, or other sale or transfer of any of the assets or business of Valley Vet, or any of our affiliates.
Please note that the entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions may not comply with all of the terms of this privacy policy.
We may disclose information about you to the government or to other third parties to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders, and subpoenas or other legal process, such as in connection with suspected illegal activity associated with the Site or our business.
We reserve the right to release information collected through the Site to law enforcement or other government officials, as we determine to be necessary or appropriate.
We may also disclose information about you to third parties if needed to enforce any of the Terms of Use or other agreements for the Site, or any investigation of potential violations of those agreements; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to protect against harm to the Site; or to protect our rights, property, or safety, or the rights, property, or safety of our users or others (for example, to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection).
Security Measures for Information We Collect
To help protect the privacy of information we collect, we employ security measures that are intended to be consistent with industry best practices.
In storing such information, we take commercially reasonable steps intended to protect such data against unauthorized access.
But please be aware that the Site is operated on software, hardware, and networks, and any component may experience breaches of security or other problems beyond our control that may compromise the security of information collected about you.
Please also be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this privacy policy, no data transmission over the Internet or via a Wi-Fi network, or any encryption method, can be guaranteed to be completely secure.
Thus, it may be possible for third parties not under Valley Vet's control to intercept or access your personal information transmitted through the Site or via email.
We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all information you provide through the Site, but due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any such information will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others who do not have your authorization.
Any such transmission of information about you to Valley Vet is at your own risk.
How to Correct or Update Information We Have Collected About You
You may correct or update information we have collected about you by contacting us at the email or mailing address noted at the end of this privacy policy, or, if available on the Site, by editing your information and preferences on your Account Information page on the Site.
You may also unsubscribe from any email subscriptions by following the applicable "unsubscribe" link.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to update our files to reflect your request as promptly as possible.
We may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, compliance with laws, fraud prevention, troubleshooting, and enforcement of our terms of use and other agreements.
Also, please note that we cannot update any information about you collected through the Site that has already been disclosed (as permitted under this privacy policy) to a third party.
How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals
The Site does not currently support "Do Not Track" preferences that may be available in your browser for letting websites know that you do not want them collecting certain kinds of information.
Specifically, if you turn on the Do Not Track setting on your browser, the Site is not currently capable of following whatever Do Not Track preferences you set.
For more information about Do Not Track, visit donottrack.us.
Transfer of Data from Outside the United States
If you use the Site from outside the United States, information that we collect about you through the Site will be transferred to servers inside the United States and maintained indefinitely.
By using the Site, you consent to the transfer of data into the United States, and the processing of such data in the United States.
Children
The Site is not designed to appeal to persons under 17 years of age (children).
We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children through the Site.
If we learn that any unauthorized personal information of a child has been collected, we will take appropriate steps to delete such information.
If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child has provided any such personal information to us, you may contact us at the email or mailing address noted at the end of this privacy policy and request that we delete that information from our systems.
Privacy Policies of any Linked Website or Other Parties
This privacy policy only addresses Valley Vet's practices for the personal and other information that we may obtain about you through the Site, or through your other communications with Valley Vet.
Please be aware that when you use or access the Site, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control, and Valley Vet is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, or the content of linked websites.
We would expect that most, if not all of these third parties will collect information about you when you use their offerings.
But Valley Vet is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, regardless of whether they are linked or otherwise connected to the Site.
We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy and terms of use whenever interacting with any third-party website, app, or other offering.
Personal Information Requests
Valley Vet works hard to provide the best customer service and online shopping experience available.
To meet that goal, we collect the types of information described in the "Information We Collect" section of this privacy policy.
And when appropriate, we share limited pieces of that information with our service providers for business purposes.
To give you more information about our privacy practices and more control over our collection and limited disclosure of your personal information, you may request we (1) disclose to you the personal information we have collected about you; (2) disclose to you the personal information about you we have shared with our service providers; (3) disclose to you the personal information about you we have sold; (4) not sell your personal information; and (5) delete the personal information we have collected about you.
You may make any of these requests online, or by calling us at 800-898-8014.
Personal Information We Have Sold In the Last 12 Months
We do not sell consumers' personal information.
Personal Information We Have Disclosed For a Business Purpose in the Last 12 Months
We have disclosed personal information to our service providers to maintain and service accounts, provide customer service, process and fulfill orders and transactions, verify customer information, authorize and process payment transactions, provide financing, provide advertising and marketing services, provide analytic services, detect and prevent fraud and security threats, provide order tracking services, calculate and remit sales taxes, expedite product rebate calculation and payment services, facilitate reporting and information-sharing regarding adverse drug events and disease control, process and deliver sweepstakes prizes and customer appreciation gifts, facilitate Live Chat communications for online customer service, send printed catalogs and product-related information, and facilitate product and site reviews.
The categories of information disclosed to our service providers include (1) identifiers, such as name, address, phone number, unique personal identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account number; (2) internet or other electronic network activity information, such as browsing history, search history, page views, and information regarding consumer interaction with our Site; (3) commercial information such as products purchased, order history, products considered, product and site reviews, and other product histories and tendencies; and (4) geolocation data.
Governing Law, Jurisdiction, and Dispute Resolution
This site (excluding any linked sites) is controlled by Valley Vet from our offices in the state of Kansas, in the United States of America.
It can be accessed from all 50 states, as well as from other countries around the world.
As each of these places has laws that may differ from those of Kansas, by accessing or attempting to access the Site, you and Valley Vet agree that any claim, cause of action, or dispute between you and Valley Vet will be governed by and construed under the statutes and laws of the state of Kansas, without regard to conflict-of-laws rules and the United Nations Convention on the International Sales of Goods.
This includes, without limitation, any claim, cause of action, or dispute relating to your use or attempted use of the Site; your interactions and communications with Valley Vet; Valley Vet's collection, use, sale, disclosure, or deletion of your personal or other information; and your privacy, whether such claims are based in contract, tort, statute, equity, or other legal basis.
You and Valley Vet agree and submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction of the state and federal courts in Kansas with respect to any claim, cause of action, or dispute.
You and Valley Vet also agree that all claims, causes of action, and disputes between you and Valley Vet are governed by the dispute resolution provisions in the Terms of Use and other agreements applicable to the Site, including the provisions for binding arbitration, waiver of the right to a jury trial, and waiver of the right to participate in a class, consolidated, or representative action.
By using or attempting to use the Site, you also agree to the limitation of liability provision in the Terms of Use and other agreements applicable to the Site for all claims, causes of action, and disputes related to your privacy, our collection, use, sale, disclosure, or deletion of your personal or other information collected through the Site or otherwise, and the issues addressed in this privacy policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We occasionally update this privacy policy, and we include the effective date of our privacy policy at the top of the statement.
We encourage you to check the Site frequently to see the current privacy policy in effect, and any changes that may have been made to it.
Your continued use of the Site after a change has been posted constitutes your acceptance of the change.
If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, your sole remedy is to discontinue your use of the Site.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy or the Site, please email us at privacy@valleyvet.com, or write to us at Valley Vet Supply, 1118 Pony Express Hwy., Marysville, Kansas
66508.
Contact Us
Shipping
Return Policy
Ordering Prescriptions
Security
Privacy
Personal Information Requests
Reset Password
Foreign Orders
CALL TOLL FREE 800-419-9524
Valley Vet SupplyCustomer Reviews
Shop by Catalog
HorseView Featured Products- - Horse Deals - -- - New Products - - - -Top Sellers- -ClippersA5 Type ClippersAll Corded A5All Cordless A5AndisLaubeOsterWahlBack to Main MenuLarge HairheadAll HairheadAndisListerOsterBack to Main MenuTrimmers & Light ClippersAll CordedAll CordlessAndisWahlBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuElectric FencingAccessoriesChargersCorral KitsInsulatorsPostsSafe-Fence Electric SystemWire WindingWire, Tape & RopeBack to Main MenuFarrier & Hoof CareFarrier's EquipmentHoof PicksMedicator & Therapy BootsThrush TreatmentTopicals & ConditionersVettec ProductsBack to Main MenuFencing SystemsCorral KitsEquipment & ToolsGate LatchesBack to Main MenuFly ControlApplicatorsFly BaitFly BootsFly Control ConcentratesFly Control SupplementsFly Long Acting InsecticidesFly Lotions & Spot ApplicationFly Masks, Collars & LegFly Premise SprayFly SheetsFly Sprays & RepellentsFly TrapsLarvae ControlNatural Sprays & WipesBack to Main MenuFor The RiderGroomingBladesA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipper PartsA5 TypeLarge ClippersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClippersA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipping AidsGrooming AidsBathing AidsCombs & BrushesDryers & VacuumsGrooming KitsMane & TailSuppliesBack to Main MenuHorse Shampoo & ConditionerColor EnhancerConditionersHair GrowthMedicatedShampoosWaterlessBack to Main MenuSharpenersBack to Main MenuHalters & LeadsCombosHaltersLeadsTrailer & Cross TiesBack to Main MenuHealth CareBandagesDiagnosticsFirst AidHomeopathic RemediesInstrumentsLinimentsPain ManagementPregnancy & Foaling AidesRespiratory TreatmentsTherapyTopicals & OintmentsWound CareBack to Main MenuHorse SupplementsBlood BuildersCalming AgentsDevelopmentDigestiveDiarrhea ControlProbioticsBack to Main MenuElectrolytesEnergyHoof BuildersInsect ControlJointHyaluronic AcidLiquid & PastePowdered/PelletBack to Main MenuMetabolic SupplementsMSMMulti-PurposeMuscle BuildingPain ManagementPerformanceRespiratorySand ColicSkin & CoatTreatsUlcer ControlVitamin & MineralWeight BuildersBack to Main MenuHorse Tack & SuppliesBitsCurb ChainsGeneralHackamoresPonyBack to Main MenuBlankets & SheetsBlanket AccessoriesBlanket WashFly SheetsHoodsLycraSheetsStableTurnoutBack to Main MenuDraftBitsBridlesCinchesFly CollarsHaltersBack to Main MenuEnglish SaddlesAll PurposeClose ContactDressagePonyBack to Main MenuEnglish TackBreastplates & MartingalesBridlesEnglish BitsGirthsSaddle AccessoriesSaddle PadsStirrupsWorking & TrainingBack to Main MenuGear & Apparel BagsHalters & LeadsCombosHaltersLeadsPersonalized HaltersTrailer & Cross TiesBack to Main MenuPacking EquipmentRoping SuppliesAccessoriesRopesBack to Main MenuSaddle AccessoriesBagsCarriers & CoversCinchesLeather CarePack EquipmentSeats & CushionsStirrup AccessoriesStirrupsBack to Main MenuSaddle Pads & BlanketsBareback PadsSaddle BlanketsSaddle PadsBack to Main MenuSafetyHelmetsMiscellaneousBack to Main MenuSports MedicineBarefoot BootsBell BootsLeg WrapsShipping BootsSkid BootsSupport BootsBack to Main MenuSpursWestern SaddlesBarrelEnduranceGaited Trail SaddlesRoperShowTrailBack to Main MenuWestern TackBitless BridlesBreast CollarsBridles & CombosHeadstallsReinsSaddle AccessoriesSnaps & HardwareSpur StrapsTack RepairWestern BitsWorking & TrainingBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuHorse VaccinesAbortion (EHV)Combination VaccinesEastern & Western CombinationsEastern, Western & Venezuelan CombinationsHorse MiscellaneousHorse RespiratoryHorse Sleeping SicknessInfluenzaPotomac Horse FeverRabiesRhino (EHV)TetanusWest Nile VirusBack to Main MenuHorse WormersAll Horse WormersContinuous Wormer - EquineDouble StrengthRegular StrengthBack to Main MenuPaste Wormer - EquineBenzimidazole Horse WormersIvermectin Horse WormersIvermectin/Praziquantel Horse WormersMoxidectin Paste/Liquid Horse WormersPyrantel Paste/Liquid Horse WormersBack to Main MenuPelleted/Powdered Wormer - EquineBack to Main MenuLeg CareBarefoot BootsBell BootsLeg WrapsShipping BootsSkid BootsSupport BootsBack to Main MenuNeedles & SyringesNeedles-DisposableSyringes-DisposableBack to Main MenuStable Equipment & SuppliesArenaBuckets & FeedersCartsCribbingForksHay Bags & RacksHeated WaterersHorse ToysJump EquipmentMiscellaneousPackSaddle & Tack RacksStallsTack BoxTraining & AccessoriesWaterersBack to Main MenuTraileringAssorted ItemsCleanerHitch RelatedJack/ChockToolboxesWateringBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuLivestockView Featured Products- - Livestock Deals - -- - New Products - -- - Top Sellers - -Cattle HealthAntibioticsArtificial InseminationEquipmentBack to Main MenuHoof CareImplantsCalfFeedlotGrowerBack to Main MenuInjectable VitaminsPinkeye ProtectionAntibioticsApplicatorsCattle Fly & LiceEyecare & TopicalsPinkeye VaccinesBack to Main MenuSupplementsColostrumMilk ReplacersShowVitamins & MineralsBack to Main MenuTopicalsWound CareBandagesInstrumentsTopicalsBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuCattle VaccinesBlackleg & PastuerellaCombinationBack to Main MenuBlackleg & PinkeyeBlackleg & SomnusBlackleg 7 & 8 WayBlackleg New AdjuvantBlackleg Original AdjuvantBack to Main MenuCalf ScoursVaccinesBack to Main MenuCow ScoursCombinationEcoliBack to Main MenuMiscellaneous VaccinesMastitisSalmonellaWart, Footrot, RabiesBack to Main MenuPinkeyePregnancy - OtherPregnancy ViralKilled VirusModified LiveBack to Main MenuRespiratory - OtherNon-ViralPastuerellaBack to Main MenuRespiratory ViralKilled VirusModified LiveBack to Main MenuTetanusBack to Main MenuCattle WormersFeed GradeIvermectinsInjectablesPour-onBack to Main MenuNon-IvermectinBack to Main MenuClippersA5 Type ClippersAll Corded A5All Cordless A5AndisLaubeOsterWahlBack to Main MenuLarge HairheadAll HairheadAndisListerOsterBack to Main MenuLarge SheepheadAll SheepheadAndisOsterPremierBack to Main MenuTrimmers & Light ClippersAll CordedAll CordlessAndisWahlBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuDairyCalcium GelsCalf SuppliesHeat Detection & BreedingKetosisMastitisSuppliesTeat & Udder TreatmentsBack to Main MenuEar TagsAgriTagsAllflexApplicators & AccessoriesDuFlexEID | RFIDFeedlot TagsInsecticide TagsNational Band and TagRitcheySheep & Goat TagsSwine TagsUSDA 840Y-TexZ TagsBack to Main MenuElectric FencingAccessoriesChargersCorral KitsInsulatorsPostsSafe-Fence Electric SystemWire WindingWire, Tape & RopeBack to Main MenuEquipment & SuppliesArtificial Insemination EquipmentGoat & Sheep EquipmentBucketsHay & Grain FeedersKid & Lamb FeedersMilkingPens & TransportScalesStands & StanchionsWater HeatersWaterersBack to Main MenuInstrumentsCap-ChurCastratingDehorningDrenchingMedical & SurgicalNeedlesNeedles-DisposableSyringesSyringes-DisposableBack to Main MenuLivestock EquipmentBuckets & FeedersCalf FeedersChutes & HeadgatesCoolingElectric Prods & SortingLivestock WaterersMonitoring DevicesScalesSwineWater HeatersBack to Main MenuMiscellaneousDisinfectantsProtective GearRat BaitBack to Main MenuOB EquipmentCattleGloves & ProtectionSheepSwineBack to Main MenuPoultry EquipmentBack to Main MenuFarm EquipmentCartsCoolingGrain and Hay TestingHeatingMiscellaneous EquipmentSpray EquipmentBack to Main MenuFencing SystemsCorral KitsEquipment & ToolsGate LatchesBack to Main MenuFly & Lice ControlApplicatorsApplicator GunsDust, Rub, PastureSpray EquipmentBack to Main MenuCattle Fly & LiceFeed Through Fly ControlFly TagsPour-on, Spray & DustBack to Main MenuFly Traps, Bait & PremiseFly BaitFly Premise SprayFly TrapsLarvae ControlBack to Main MenuSwine Fly & Lice ControlSpray, Pour-on & DustBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuGoat & SheepFencingChargersElectric Fence AccessoriesElectric NettingInsulatorsPostsWire & TapeWire Fence EquipmentBack to Main MenuFly & LiceSpray EquipmentTopical InsecticidesTraps, Bait & PremiseBack to Main MenuGoat & Sheep EquipmentBucketsHay & Grain FeedersKid & Lamb FeedersMilkingPens & TransportScalesStands & StanchionsWater HeatersWaterersBack to Main MenuHealth CareCastration & DehorningHoof CareIdentificationInstrumentsOral MedicationsOral Syringes & DrenchingSulfa & AntibioticsSyringes & NeedlesWound CareBack to Main MenuNutritionColostrum & MilkEnergy & ElectrolytesProbiotics & DigestionShow SupplementsTreatsVitamins & MineralsBack to Main MenuOBBreedingKidding & LambingBack to Main MenuRestraints & WorkingShow & GroomingBrushes & CombsClipping & ShearingFitting Stands & EquipmentHalters, Leads & TubesPens & TransportShampoo & StylingSupplementsBack to Main MenuVaccinesC & DCaseous LymphadenitisCD & TMiscellaneousTetanusBack to Main MenuWormersBack to Main MenuLivestock IdentificationBrandsFreezeHotBack to Main MenuID Tags840 USDAApplicators & AccessoriesCattleEID | RFIDFeedlotSheepSwineBack to Main MenuPaintTattooLivestockPetBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuNeedles & SyringesCap-ChurDrenchingNeedlesNeedles-DisposableSyringesSyringes-DisposableBack to Main MenuOral MedicationsCoccidiosisDiarrhea & ScourColostrumDiarrhea ControlScour ControlBack to Main MenuElectrolytesCalfCattleBack to Main MenuFeed MedicationsMiscellaneousProbioticsFeedPaste & BolusSulfa & AntibioticsWater & MilkBack to Main MenuSulfa & AntibioticsBack to Main MenuPoultry HealthPoultry EquipmentBucketsCoops & PensFeedersIncubation & EggWater HeatersWaterersBack to Main MenuPoultry FeedPoultry Fly & Insect ControlBait & PremisePoultry SpraySpray EquipmentTrapsBack to Main MenuPoultry MedicationsWater MedicationsBack to Main MenuPoultry Needles & SyringesPoultry SupplementsPoultry TopicalsPoultry VaccinesBack to Main MenuShowing & GroomingAdhesives & StylingAdhesives & StylingConditionersHair ColoringHair SheenShampoo & BreakdownBack to Main MenuClipper BladesA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadSheep Head CombsSheep Head CuttersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipper PartsA5 TypeLarge ClippersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClippersA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadLarge Sheep HeadTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipping AidsEquipmentBathing AidsBlocking ChutesBlowersFans & StandsShow BoxesBack to Main MenuSharpenersShow Alpaca & LlamaHalters & LeadsBack to Main MenuShow CattleBlocking ChutesHalters & LeadsShow SticksSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow GoatBlankets & TubesFitting StandsHair PreparationHalters, Collars & LeadsSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow PigBrushesHair PreparationShow Sticks & BatsSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow RabbitSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow SheepBlankets & TubesFitting StandsHair PreparationHalters & LeadsRakes & Wool CombsSupplementsBack to Main MenuSuppliesBrushes & CombsExhibitor's SuppliesScissors & ShearsSprayers & FoggersStall SuppliesBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuSwine HealthSwine AntibioticsSwine Fly & Lice ControlSwine IronSwine Oral MedicationsEnergy & ElectrolytesFeedProbiotics & DigestionWaterBack to Main MenuSwine SupplementsSwine WormersBack to Main MenuSwine VaccinesBreedingMiscellaneousRespiratoryRhinitisScoursBack to Main MenuTraileringAssorted ItemsCleanerHitch RelatedJack/ChockToolboxesWateringBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuPetView Featured Products- - New Products - - - - Pet Deals - -- - Top Sellers - -AntibioticsCalming AgentsCat PheromonesCat SupplementsComfort ZoneDog PheromonesDog SupplementsBack to Main MenuCat SuppliesBedsCalming AgentsCare & ToysCollars & LeashesDietary SupportFlea & Tick ControlHairball RemediesRespiratory & Eye HealthTreatsBack to Main MenuCat VaccinesChews & RawhideChinchilla SuppliesFeeders & WaterersNutritional SupplementsTreatsBack to Main MenuClippersA5 Type ClippersAll Corded A5All Cordless A5AndisLaubeOsterWahlBack to Main MenuTrimmers & Light ClippersAll CordedAll CordlessAndisWahlBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuClothing & AccessoriesDog BlanketsDog BootsBack to Main MenuCold Weather ProductsDog BlanketsHeated Pet BedsHeated Pet BowlsProtectionBack to Main MenuDog BedsDog BlanketsDog Breeding SuppliesArtificial InseminationDewormerDisposable Gloves and BootsKennelsSemen CollectionSupplementsSyringes and NeedlesVaccinesBack to Main MenuDog ToysDog TreatsDog Vaccines5-Way + Coronavirus Vaccines5-Way Vaccines7-Way + Coronavirus Vaccines7-Way VaccinesBordatella + Parainfluenza VaccinesMiscellaneous Dog VaccinesParvo and/or Cornavirus VaccinesRabies VaccinesSingle Dose Dog VaccinesBack to Main MenuFlea & Tick ControlFlea & Tick Cat CollarsFlea & Tick Dog CollarsFlea & Tick Foggers & PremiseFlea & Tick Oral MedicationsFlea & Tick ShampoosFlea & Tick Sprays, Dips & PowdersFlea & Tick TopicalsInsect ShieldBack to Main MenuGrooming (Pet)BladesA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadSheep Head CombsSheep Head CuttersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClippersA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadLarge Sheep HeadTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipping AidsGrooming AidsCombs & BrushesDryers & VacuumsNail Trimmers & ScissorsBack to Main MenuPartsA5 TypeLarge ClippersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuShampoos & ConditionersColognesConditionersGentle & TearlessMedicatedBack to Main MenuSharpenersBack to Main MenuHealthArtificial InseminationBandagesDentalDisinfectantsEar CareEye CareFly & Mosquito ControlHomeopathicInstrumentsTopicals & Paw CareBack to Main MenuNeedles & SyringesNeedles-DisposableSyringes-DisposableBack to Main MenuPet Equipment & SuppliesCages & KennelsCagesCrate Mats & AccessoriesHeat PadsHousesKennels & EquipmentBack to Main MenuCold MaintenanceCollars & LeashesDog CollarsDog HarnessDog LeashesBack to Main MenuDog BedsDog Fencing & ContainmentDog Doors, Gates & PensBack to Main MenuExercise EquipmentFood & Water SolutionsFeedersWaterersBack to Main MenuInsect ShieldAccessoriesBedsKennel & EquipmentPet ApparelBack to Main MenuPet Chews & RawhideChewsDental ChewsRawhideBack to Main MenuPet TrainingAccessoriesBoundary AidsTraining DevicesBack to Main MenuPet Travel & SafetyBowls & FeedersSafety & TagsBack to Main MenuPet Waste ManagementHousebreaking & IncontinenceStain & Odor RemoverWaste DisposalBack to Main MenuToysBack to Main MenuRabbit SuppliesEquipment & SuppliesFeeders & WaterersHutches & CagesNutrition SupplementsTopicalsTreatsBack to Main MenuSupplementsCalming AgentsDigestiveEnergy, Mother & PuppyJoint SupplementsLiver SupportMilk ReplacersRenal FunctionSenior CareSkin & CoatVitamins & MineralsBack to Main MenuVaccinesCat VaccinesDog VaccinesBack to Main MenuWormersBack to Main MenuPharmacyView Featured ProductsCat RxAllergyAntibioticsBehaviorDigestiveEarElectrolytesEyeFoodHeart & Blood PressureHeartworm PreventionHormoneInsulin & DiabetesLiver & PancreaticNeedles & SyringesPain & InflammationTopicalsUrinary & KidneyWormerBack to Main MenuDog RxAllergyAntibioticsArthritis, Pain & InflammationBehaviorDigestiveEarElectrolytesEpilepsy & SeizureExternal Parasite TreatmentEyeFoodHeart & Blood PressureHeartworm PreventionHeartworm Prevention + FleaHormoneInsulin & DiabetesLiver & PancreaticNeedles & SyringesTopicalsUrinary & KidneyVitaminsWormerBack to Main MenuHorse RxAntibacterial & AntiprotozoalAntibioticsColicEdemaElectrolytesInflammation & PainJoint DysfunctionMetabolicMuscle RelaxantsNavicularNeedles & SyringesReproductiveRespiratorySedation & AnesthesiaTopicalsToxic ConditionsUlcer & DigestionVitaminsWormerBack to Main MenuLivestock RxAntibioticsDairyElectrolytesInflammation and PainMiscellaneousNeedles & SyringesReproductiveSwineVitaminsBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuApparel & FootwearView Featured Products- - New Products - -Mens BootsAll Mens FootwearMens Casual FootwearMens Chore BootsMens Cowboy BootsMens Endurance FootwearBack to Main MenuMens ClothingMens Chinks & ChapsMens Conceal & Carry OutwearMens GlovesMens JeansMens OuterwearMens Riding GearMens ShirtsBack to Main MenuWomens BootsAll Womens FootwearWomens Casual FootwearWomens Chore BootsWomens Cowboys BootsWomens Endurance FootwearWomens English FootwearBack to Main MenuWomens ClothingWomens Chinks & ChapsWomens Conceal & Carry OutwearWomens Gloves, Hats & AccessoriesWomens JeansWomens OuterwearWomens Riding GearWomens ShirtsWomens UndergarmentsBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuFencingView Featured ProductsCorral KitsElectric FencingAccessoriesChargersCorral KitsInsulatorsPostsSafe-Fence Electric SystemWire WindingWire, Tape & RopeBack to Main MenuEquipment & ToolsGate LatchesBack to Main MenuShow SuppliesView Featured ProductsAdhesives & StylingBathing AidsBlowersBrushes & CombsClipper BladesA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadSheep Head CombsSheep Head CuttersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClippersA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadLarge Sheep HeadTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipping AidsConditionersExhibitor's SuppliesFans & StandsHair ColoringHair SheenScissors & ShearsShampoo & BreakdownSharpenersShow Alpaca & LlamaShow BoxesShow CattleBlocking ChutesHalters & LeadsShow SticksSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow GoatBlankets & TubesFitting StandsHair PreparationHalters, Collars & LeadsSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow PigBrushesHair PreparationShow Sticks & BatsSupplementsBack to Main MenuShow RabbitShow SheepBlankets & TubesFitting StandsHair PreparationHalters & LeadsRakes & Wool CombsSupplementsBack to Main MenuSprayers & FoggersStall SuppliesBack to Main MenuGoat & SheepView Featured ProductsCastration & DehorningEquipmentBucketsCartsHay & Grain FeedersKid & Lamb FeedersMilkingPens & TransportRestraints & WorkingScalesStands & StanchionsWater HeatersWaterersBack to Main MenuFencingChargersElectric Fence AccessoriesElectric NettingInsulatorsPostsWire & TapeWire Fence EquipmentBack to Main MenuFly & LiceSpray EquipmentTopical InsecticidesTraps, Bait & PremiseBack to Main MenuHealth CareIdentificationInstrumentsOral MedicationsOral Syringes & DrenchingSulfa & AntibioticsSyringes & NeedlesWound CareBack to Main MenuHoof CareNeedles & SyringesDrenchingNeedlesNeedles-DisposableSyringesSyringes-DisposableBack to Main MenuNutritionColostrum & MilkEnergy & ElectrolytesProbiotics & DigestionShow SupplementsTreatsVitamins & MineralsBack to Main MenuOBBreedingKidding & LambingBack to Main MenuShow & GroomingBrushes & CombsClipper BladesA5 TypeLarge Hair HeadSharpenersSheep Head CombsSheep Head CuttersTrimmers & LightBack to Main MenuClipping & ShearingFitting Stands & EquipmentHalters, Leads & TubesShampoo & StylingSupplementsBack to Main MenuVaccinesC & DCaseous LymphadenitisCD & TMiscellaneousTetanusBack to Main MenuWormersBack to Main MenuClearanceView Featured ProductsApparel & FootwearMensWomensBack to Main MenuFarmHome DecorHorsePetBack to Main MenuBrooksideView Featured ProductsBitsBlankets & SheetsBlanket AccessoriesDog BlanketsHoodsLycraSheetsStableTurnoutsBack to Main MenuCinchesGear & Apparel BagsHalters & LeadsHaltersBack to Main MenuPadsSports MedicineBell BootsShipping BootsSupport BootsBack to Main MenuSpursStable Equipment & SuppliesSupplementsCalmingDigestiveEnergyHoof BuildersJointMSMMulti-PurposeRespiratorySkin & CoatVitamins & MineralsBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuGift GivingView Featured Products- Gift Card Promo- Gift DealsApparel & FootwearView Apparel & Footwear- - New Products - -Mens BootsAll Mens FootwearMens Casual FootwearMens Chore BootsMens Cowboy BootsMens Endurance FootwearBack to Main MenuMens ClothingMens Chinks & ChapsMens Conceal & Carry OutwearMens GlovesMens JeansMens OuterwearMens Riding GearMens ShirtsBack to Main MenuWomens BootsAll Womens FootwearWomens Casual FootwearWomens Chore BootsWomens Cowboys BootsWomens Endurance FootwearWomens English FootwearBack to Main MenuWomens ClothingWomens Chinks & ChapsWomens Conceal & Carry OutwearWomens Gloves, Hats & AccessoriesWomens JeansWomens OuterwearWomens Riding GearWomens ShirtsWomens UndergarmentsBack to Main MenuBack to Main MenuBack On TrackCircle YEquibrandFor Your HorsePersonalizedSaddle PadsSupport BootsTack - CinchesTack - HeadstallsToysTreatsBack to Main MenuFor Your PetCages & KennelsCat ToysCat TreatsChews & TreatsCollars & LeashesCrate MatsDog BedsDog Coats & BlanketsDog ToysGrooming AidsHeat PadsPersonalizedPet Gift SetsRawhideTreat DispensersBack to Main MenuFor Your Rider & Barn FriendsBooks & SoftwareGrooming SetsHome DecorKids ToysPersonalizedSaddle BagsSaddle RacksBack to Main MenuHigh HorseHorsewearPerri LeatherPro ChoiceReinsmanTucker SaddleryBack to Main Menu
EducationSupporting the health of your horses, livestock and pets.
Get exclusive offers, coupons, and limited-time discounts delivered to your inbox.
Sign up today and save!
SIGN UP!
X
Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy have changed. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
